Joey?
Are you in there?
God, that's Rachel!
Joey, you have to talk to her.
Oh, no, I can't, I can't.
Not after the other night.
It's too weird, okay?
Don't tell her I'm here.
Don't eat that!
Hi.
Hey, Rachel.
Is Joey here?
I don't see him.
Do you see him?
Hey, maybe he's
in the sugar bowl.
Joey? No.
( both laugh )
Well, at least you make
each other laugh.
What's up?
Well, I haven't seen him
since the night that he told me
how he, you know...
I don't know, I think
he's avoiding me.
Why is that bagel
on the floor?
We were playing
a game.
Ew, was Chandler naked?
Sort of like a ring-toss
kind of situation?
Sure.
What? No... no!
All right, well, listen,
if you see Joey
will you just tell him
that, uh... I miss him.
( door closes )
Okay, did you hear that?
Yeah, that naked bagel game?
Dude, I don't know.
That's a pretty small hole.
Honey, you've got
to talk to her.
I can't.
You guys don't know
what it's like
to put yourself out there
like that
and then just get shot down.
I don't know
what that's like?
Up until I was 25
I thought the only
response to "I love you"
was, "Oh, crap."
And hello--
no rejection?
I got shot down
at fat camp.
Boy, kids are mean
when they're hungry.
All right, so what do I do?
This is Rachel.
What are you going to do--
never talk to her again?
I know it's weird,
it's awkward
but you got to
at least try.
Yeah, okay.
Whoa! Almost forgot
this was on your...
We didn't play it!
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Okay, so when you're done
with your tea
I'll look at the leaves
and tell you your fortune.
I didn't know
you read tea leaves.
Oh, yeah. I've
done it for years.
I actually stopped
because I was so accurate.
You know and... you know
one of the great joys
of life
is its wondrous
unpredictability, you know.
And also tea tends
to give me the trots.
Okay, I'm done.
Read mine.
Okay... Ooh.
I see a ladder...
which can mean
either a promotion
or a violent death.
I'm a head chef.
I can't get promoted.
Mm-hmm, Mm-hmm...
who's next?
Okay, I'm done.
Do mine.
Okay.
Um... oh, okay.
I see a circle.
Oh, which can either mean
you're having a baby
or you're going to make
a scientific discovery.
Well, I have been spending
a lot of time in the lab.
What does yours say, Pheebs?
Well, all right.
Wow... yay!
Oh, I'm going to meet a guy!
And really soon!
And he's going to be
the man of my dreams.
Probably not the guy
I had a dream about last night.
Hey, has anyone seen my shirt?
It's button-down,
like a faded salmon color.
You mean
your pink shirt?
Faded salmon color.
No, I haven't seen
your pink shirt.
Great, great.
I must have left it at Mona's.
I knew it.
I'm sure you can get another one
at Ann Taylor's.
That's my favorite shirt, okay?
I love that shirt.
Just ask Mona to give it back.
I don't know.
I mean, I guess I could.
It's just, we didn't really
end things on such good terms.
And if I went over there
I'd be ignoring the one thing
she asked me to do
when we broke up:
jump up my own ass and die.
Oh, wait a second,
you guys.
For the last couple
of weeks
I've been seeing that guy
everywhere I go.
We take the same bus,
we go to the same bookstores
same dry cleaners...
May be he's the tea guy.
Pheebs,
did you see that?
He totally checked you out
and he is so cute!
Mine is a picture
of the Village People.
What does that mean?
Hi.
Hey.
Tea gives Phoebe
the trots.
So, I thought Joey and I
would be okay
once we hung out
but it's like we
don't even know
how to be with each
other anymore.
I know it's tough now,
but things'll get better.
How do you know that?
What if it just
gets worse and
worse and worse
to the point where
we can't even be
in the same room
with each other?
I'm not great at the advice.
Can I interest you
in a sarcastic comment?
Some cheese?
Honey...
why is the Bruce Springsteen CD
in the Cat Stevens case?
Let's just say if I can't find
the right CD case
I just put it
in the nearest one.
Okay, well, where is
the Cat Stevens CD?
In the James Taylor case.
Where's the James Taylor CD?
Honey, I'm going to save you
some time.
200 CDs, not one of them
in the right case.
Okay, no need to panic.
Deep breaths everyone.
Okay, um, we're just going
to have to spend some time
and put the CDs
in the right cases.
Then we should come up
with some kind of order.
You know, like alphabetically
or by genre.
Mmm, I don't know.
I think we're going
to have to talk this through.
Oh, my God, you guys
have such problems.
I feel so terrible for you.
Okay, I-I'm sorry.
Look, you and Joey
you're both focusing
on this uncomfortable thing.
What you need to do
is change the subject.
Next time you see him
try to get him talking
about something else.
Oh, yeah, that makes sense.
Yeah, like, I don't know
maybe you have
a work problem
that you need his advice on.
Ooh, I could do that.
Good.
I could do that.
Honey, the Miami Vice
soundtrack? Really?
They were just giving those away
at the store.
In exchange for money.
Hey.
Hi.
I really don't know
what to tell you, Rach.
I really don't.
I mean, maybe Joey
could help you out
with your big work problem.
What?
Yeah, Joey, she's...
Rachel's got this really
big work problem.
It is a head-scratcher.
Wow, you know what?
If we're going to make dinner
we're going to have to leave.
Yeah.
So, you, uh,
have a big work problem?
Yeah, it's, um...
Yeah... it's, uh...
It's noth...
you know, it's nothing.
Oh, okay.
So, uh, I think
I'm going to take off.
No, wait, Joey, no, wait.
It is. It's something.
It's-it's, um...
It's my boss.
Yeah?
Yeah, and, um...
and my baby.
Yeah?
My boss wants to buy my baby.
What?
Oh, my... oh, my God.
I know, I told you
it's a really big problem.
What... he wants
to buy your baby?
Can you believe that?
That's crazy.
That's what I told him.
Okay, how did this
even happen?
Well, I'll tell you...
See, my-my boss and, uh...
and his wife,
they can't have children
so, um, and then when we were
at the Christmas party
and he got drunk
and he said to me
"Rachel,
I want to buy your baby."
Man. When you said
it was a problem
about your boss
and the baby
I figured it was something
about maternity leave.
Oh... yeah...
Yeah, that would have been
a much simpler problem.
Oh, hello.
Oh.
It's you.
I see you everywhere.
Mm-hmm.
I'm Jim. Jim Nelson.
Oh, Jim-Jim Nelson,
I'm Phoebe-Phoebe Buffay.
We certainly
have been seeing
a lot of each other lately.
We have.
Maybe we'll be
seeing each other
at dinner tomorrow night.
Say around 8:00?
Well, maybe we will.
Oh!
Mona?
( falsetto yelp )
Okay, if I were a salmon shirt,
where would I be?
( keys rattling )
I am so sorry I spilled wine
all over your shirt.
Oh, it's okay.
No, it's still wet.
You know what?
Let me get it out
before it sets.
Oh, I have something
you could wear.
Here.
Oh, uh...
I don't know if I want
to wear a woman's shirt.
No, no, that's a man's shirt.
Awfully pink.
Oh, my God, honey
we are so meant
to be together.
Look, we both have copies
of the Annie soundtrack.
Honey, both yours.
Hey, great advice
on that Joey thing.
Yeah? The work problem?
Oh, it was perfect.
I mean, it really felt
like he was my friend again.
What problem did you
tell him you have?
Oh, that's-that's not important.
The point is, I really...
I think everything's
going to be okay.
May I help you?
You think you can just
buy my friend's baby?
Isn't it funny
how we kept running
into each other?
It's as if someone
really wants us
to be together.
Someone does.
Me.
Ooh, witty banter.
Well done.
Thank you.
So tell me a little bit
about yourself.
Oh, okay.
Well, I'm a masseuse.
And I used to work
at this place...
Do you like to... party?
I... I... I like parties.
You're wild, aren't you?
I gue... Yeah, I guess a little.
That ain't no thing.
I'm wild, too.
So, um, anyway...
I-I I've lived in New York
somewhat wildly, I guess
for, um... well,
since I was 14.
I'm sorry.
I'm staring.
It's just that you have
the most beautiful eyes.
Oh, stop it.
And your breasts... Mm!
Okay, look, you're coming on
a little strong.
But I'm going to give you
the benefit of the doubt
because it seems the universe
really wants us to be together.
So why don't we just start over,
okay?
You can just tell
me about yourself.
All right.
Okay.
I write erotic novels...
for children.
What?
They're wildly unpopular.
Oh, my God.
Oh, also
you might be interested to know
that I have a PhD.
Wow, you do?
Yep, a pretty huge...
All right.
♪ The sun will come out
tomorrow ♪
♪ Bet... your bottom dollar
that tomorrow... ♪
( with manly voice ):
♪ There'll be sun. ♪
Hey.
ALL:
Oh, Joey, hey, listen
thank you for
talking to me yesterday
about that thing
with my boss.
That really meant a lot.
Not a problem.
Oh, and just so you know
that guy's not going to be
bothering you
about that baby thing anymore.
What?
Let's just say
I took care of it.
Oh, let's say more.
What? Don't worry.
Don't worry.
I just told him,
very nicely
you don't go buying
people's babies
so back off.
What?!
No, no, no, no, no.
Joey, he doesn't want
to buy my baby.
I made that up.
What?!
Why?
So that we would have
something to talk about.
So it wouldn't be awkward.
And you couldn't think
of anything else?
You said your boss wants
to buy your baby?
I can't believe
you yelled at my boss.
I'm going to lose my job.
What am I going to do?
You could always sell your baby.
Joey, I cannot believe
you brought
my boss into this.
I'm going to get fired.
You lied to me.
Well, she told me to.
Chandler has two copies
of Annie.
Huh.
Oh, my God!
Ross!
Hello!
Ross, what
are you doing?
Not touching myself
if that makes anyone
less uncomfortable.
( knocking )
Good morning.
You wanted to see me?
Please, come in.
Have a seat.
Okay, look, Mr. Zelner...
Oh, I think it's best
that I speak first.
I've asked Lee
from Human Resources
to be here as a witness
to our conversation.
Oh, God.
If I in any way implied
that I wanted
to buy your baby...
I am sorry, okay?
Last week when I asked you
when your due date was
I certainly did not mean
that I felt that I was
due your baby.
Yeah, I want
to be
very clear
that I understand
that it's your baby
and that it's not mine
to purchase.
Well, as long as we are clear
about that.
Oh, there it is.
That's not your
regular dry cleaners.
I know,
but that creep
I went on that date
with goes there
so I had to find
a new one.
I also have to find
a new video store
a new bank, a new
adult bookstore
a new grocery store...
What?
A new grocery store.
The universe said I was
going to meet a nice guy
and that's what they gave me?
When I get up there
I'm going to kick
some ass.
Don't worry, Phoebe.
You're going
to meet the one.
If I can meet
a great guy
so can you.
Yeah, we both can.
And we both will.
Well, you didn't have
to come in with me.
Are you kidding?
This is where
they get out stains.
This is like
Disneyland for me.
I'm going to be
over here
watching "The Dance
of the Clean Shirts.
Oh, excuse me.
I think you dropped...
Wow.
What?
I'm sorry, it's just
that you're so
incredibly beautiful.
Oh, yeah, well,
I'm sorry about that, too
but what are you
going to do?
I hope you don't
think I'm crazy
but I feel like
I was meant to
pick this up.
Do you believe
in that kind of thing?
A little.
Now you're talking.
Would you like to go
have a cup of coffee?
I'd-I'd love to.
Let me just
tell my friend.
Ooh, an ink stain.
Hey, can I watch
how you get this out?
She must have left.
Hi.
So, what happened?
It's all going
to be okay.
They are just
so happy that
I'm not suing them
that they gave me
one extra month
paid maternity leave.
So long as I understand
that the money should not be
construed as a down payment
on this, or any other child
that I may bear.
Wow, Ralph Lauren is really
going out of their way
to show that they're not
in the baby buying business.
Chandler, can you
give us a minute?
Oh, I'm sorry.
You're going
to kick me out
of my own living room?
Yeah.
I'll be in there.
( clearing throat )
Joey, I'm really sorry
that I lied to you.
I was just trying
to make things...
I know.
But it kind of worked.
I mean, you know,
I don't know about you
but I haven't thought
about our thing
since all this.
Yeah, you're right.
Yeah, it's kind
of been like us again
a little bit.
Yeah, I know.
I miss that.
Me, too.
I mean, I haven't
thought at all
about how I put
myself out there
and said all that stuff
and how you didn't feel
the same way about me
and... and how it was...
really awkward.
My gynecologist
tried to kill me.
Item J-4-3-7-A.
Color-- winterberry.
( knocking )
Hi.
Um, listen, come here... come...
I'm so, so sorry
about yesterday.
I'm really
really sorry.
It's just I...
Listen, Ross, you
don't have to apologize.
I understand
why you were there.
You do?
Yeah. You still have
feelings for me
and... and to be honest
I still have feelings
for you too
and I wish we could
work it out, Ross
but we can't.
It's too complicated
with you
and Rachel
and the baby.
I just...
It just wasn't
meant to be.
Oh, God, you're right.
Ross, we... we have
to be strong.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, I'm going to go.
Can I... to remember you?
No.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org